Preliminary Inventory of the Ohio State University, Internal Audit Records, 1897-2000 RG.6.B.2
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Accession Number UA.2000.0077, 1977-1997; 20.4 Cubic feet; (17) cartons
  - Project No. 4501-91030: Student Personnel Asst. Program, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 4288-90077: Wexner Center, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 4288-91123: Wexner Center, 1991 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 4540-95002: Student Health Services, 1994 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 4560-93306: Recreational and Intramural Sports, 1993 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 4570-91053: Disability Services, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 4600-90076: Health Services Admin., 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 11)
  - Project No. 4604-90122: Cancer Hospital and Research Inst., 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 12)
  - Project No. 4640-90124: Nisonger Center for Mental Retardation, 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 13)
  - Project No. 4625-91056: Geriatrics, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 14)
  - Project No. 4700-93004: Human Resources, 1992 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 15)
  - Project No. 4700-91126: Personnel Services - Benefits, 1991 June (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 16)
  - Project No. 4700-91128: Personnel Services - ID Center, 1991 June (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 17)
  - Project No. 4720-95009:Human Resources Services, 1994 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 18)
  - Project No. 4700-91125:Personnel Services - Compensation, 1991 June (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 19)
  - Project No. 4710-91127: Personnel Services - Child Care Center, 1991 June (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 20)
  - Project No. 4800-91059: University Communications, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 21)
  - Project No. 5014-91064: Internal Audit, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 22)
  - Project No. 5014-92007: Internal Audit, 1991 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 23)
  - Project No. 5081-91067: Wexner Center Security, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 24)
  - Project No. 5039-91065: Receiving Department, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 25)
  - Project No. 5155-90078: Office Equipment Repair, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 26)
  - Project No. 0151-96058: Conferences and Institutes, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 27)
  - Project No. 0200-94018: Arts Admin., 1993 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 28)
  - Project No. 0210-96059: Advanced Computing, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 29)
  - Project No. 0215-95050 Department of Art, 1995 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 30)
  - Project No. 0225-96061: Art Education, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 31)
  - Project No. 0241-96063: Dance, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 32)
  - Project No. 0262-95065: School of Music, 1995 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 33)
  - Project No. 0326-95059: Department of Gen. Biology, 1995 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 34)
  - Project No. 0330-96066: Entomology, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 35)
  - Project No. 0340-95064: Department of Molecular Genetics, 1995 Janurary (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 36)
  - Project No. 0350-96071: Microbiology, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 37)
  - Project No. 0380-96072: Plant biology, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 38)
  - Project No. 0500-96073: Humanities Admin., 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 39)
  - Project No. 0509-95070: Department of Classics, 1995 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 40)
  - Project No. 0537-95086: Department of English, 1995 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 41)
  - Project No. 0543-95058: Foreign Language Center, 1995 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 42)
  - Project No. 0545-96027: Department of French and Italian, 1995 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 43)
  - Project No. 0547-96035: Department of Germanic Languages, 1995 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 44)
  - Project No. 0557-96043: Department of History, 1995 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 45)
  - Project No. 0566-94028: Linguistics, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 0600-96075: Mathematical and Physical Sciences, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 0628-95114: Department of Chemistry, 1995 June (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 0656-96076: Geological Science, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 0671-96077: Mathematics, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 0703-95089: Center for Human Resource Research, 1995 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 0703-90082: Human Resource Research Center, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 0704-96080: WOSU Stations, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 0706-95093: University Press, 1995 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 0711-96007: Department of Antheopology, 1995 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 0766-96082: Psychology, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 11)
  - Project No. 0777-95062: Department of Sociology, 1995 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 12)
  - Project No. 0896-95036: ATI - Student Services, 1994 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 13)
  - Project No. 0928-95047: Lima Campus, 1995 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 14)
  - Project No. 0942-96039: Mansfield Campus, 1995 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 15)
  - Project No. 1014-94039: Accounting and Management Information, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 16)
  - Project No. 1050-96034: Department of Marketing, 1995 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 17)
  - Project No. 1056-96044: Executive Education, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 18)
  - Project No. 1070-96084: Business Support Services, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 19)
  - Project No. 1118-95085: Department of Agricultural Education, 1995 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 20)
  - Project No. 1156-90101: Food Science and Technology, 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 21)
  - Project No. 1156-94045: Food Science and Technology, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 22)
  - Project No. 1173-96015: School of Natural Resources, 1995 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 23)
  - Project No. 1200-96090: Education Administration, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 24)
  - Project No. 1203-94049: Center on Education and Training, 1994 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 25)
  - Project No. 1204-95081: Faculty and TA Development, 1995 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 26)
  - Project No. 1220-94050: Department of Educational Policy and Leader, 1994 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 27)
  - Project No. 1241-97136: English As A Second Language, 1997 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 28)
  - Project No. 1270-97092: School of Physical Activity, 1997 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 29)
  - Project No. 1275-97093: School of Teaching and Learning, 1997 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 30)
  - Project No. 1425-94053: Department of Chemical Engineering, 1994 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 31)
  - Project No. 1435-96093: Computer and Info Science, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 32)
  - Project No. 1452-95099: Engineering Experiment Station, 1995 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 33)
  - Project No. 1468-95071: Department of Materials Science, 1995 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 34)
  - Project No. 1500-96091: Human ecology Admin., 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 35)
  - Project No. 1501-94058: Department of Family Relations and Human Development, 1994 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 36)
  - Project No. 1504-96045: Department of Human Nutrition and Food Management, 1995 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 37)
  - Project No. 1730-96032: Department of Community, Parent-Child, 1995 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 38)
  - Project No. 1750-96026: Adult Health and Illness Nursing, 1995 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 39)
  - Project No. 2100-94059: Office of Dentistry Admin., 1994 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 40)
  - Project No. 2105-94060: Dentistry, 1994 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 41)
  - Project No. 2510-94063: Department of Cell Biology, Neurobiology, 1994 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 42)
  - Project No. 2513-94064: Department of Family Medicine, 1994 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 43)
  - Project No. 2525-95104: Department of Internal Medicine, 1995 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 44)
  - Project No. 2528-94065: Department of Neurology, 1994 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 45)
  - Project No. 2535-94066: Department of Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1994 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 46)
  - Project No. 2540-94067: Department of Ophthalmology, 1994 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 47)
  - Project No. 2545-94070: Department of Otolaryngology, 1994 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 48)
  - Project No. 2550-90044: Pathology, 1990 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 49)
  - Project No. 2555-95063, 1995 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 50)
  - Project No. 2560-94071: Department of Pharmcacology, 1994 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 51)
  - Project No. 2565-94072: Department of Physical Medicine, 1994 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 52)
  - Project No. 2570-94073: Department of Medical Biochemistry, 1994 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 53)
  - Project No. 2575-94074: Department of Physiology, 1994 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 54)
  - Project No. 2595-94075: Department of Surgery, 1994 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 55)
  - Project No. 2900-94076: Office of Veterinary Medicine Admin, 1994 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 56)
  - Project No. 2927-96108: Vet Hospital, 1996 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 57)
  - Project No. 2940-95055: Department of Veterinary Biosciences, 1995 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 58)
  - Project No. 3200-98068: University Libraries, 1998 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 59)
  - Project No. 3200-94082: University Libraries, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 60)
  - Project No. 3500-96111: Board of Trustees, 1996 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 61)
  - Project No. 3700-95117: Office of Legal Affairs Admin, 1995 June (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 62)
  - Project No. 3900-95098: Office of VP for Finance Admin., 1995 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 63)
  - Project No. 3941-95049: Division of Accounting, 1995 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 64)
  - Project No. 4004-94084: Campus Chemical Instrument Center, 1994 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 65)
  - Project No. 4005-94085: Campus Microscopy and Imaging, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 66)
  - Project No. 4007-95080: Center for Mapping, 1995 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 67)
  - Project No. 4010-94086: Center for Molecular Environ. Health, 1994 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 68)
  - Project No. 4010-95096: Office of OSURF Admin., 1995 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 69)
  - Project No. 4054-95113: Center for Lake Erie Area Research, 1995 June (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 70)
  - Project No. 4217-95048: Office of the University Registrar, 1995 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 71)
  - Project No. 4500-94091: Office of Student Affairs, 1994 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 72)
  - Project No. 4515-95001: Office of Student Life, 1994 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 73)
  - Project No. 4600-95090: Office of the VP for Health Science Admin., 1995 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 74)
  - Project No. 4605-95004: OSU Comprehensive Cancer Center, 1994 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 75)
  - Project No. 4605-90079: Cancer Center, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 76)
  - Project No. 4615-95043: Center for Health Policy Standards, 1994 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 77)
  - Project No. 4057-95037: Neurobiotechnology Center, 1994 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 78)
  - Project No. 4640-95005: Nisonger Center, 1994 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 79)
  - Project No. 4720-96128: Human Resources/Compensation, 1996 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 80)
  - Project No. 4730-95067: Office of the Employee Relations, 1995 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 81)
  - Project No. 4900-95094: Office of the VP for University Dev., 1995 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 82)
  - Project No. 5035-95039: Purchasing Dept, 1994 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 83)
  - Project No. 5449-95025: Ohio/Drake Unions, 1994 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 84)
  - Project No. 5477-95024: University Airport, 1994 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 85)
  - Project No. 5501-95026: OSUE Administration, 1994 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 86)
  - Project No. 5694-95095: OARDC = Outlying Branches, 1995 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 87)
  - Project No. 5698-95078: OARDC - Research operations, 1995 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0016, Folder 88)
  - Project No. 0575-96029: Department of Philosophy, 1995 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 0744-96018: School of Journalism, 1995 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 0280-96064: Theatre, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 0321: Biological Sciences, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 1470-96095: Mechanical Engineering, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 0300-96065: Biological Sciences Admin., 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 1280-97094: Education Policy and Leadership, 1997 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 1445-96094: Electrical Engineering, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 1039-97109: Management and Human Resources, 1997 November (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 0700-96021: Office of Social and Behavioral Science, 1995 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 0150-96057: Continuing Education, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 11)
  - Project No. 0230-96062: Industrial Desgin, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 12)
  - Project No. 4570-95091: Office of Disability Services, 1995 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 13)
  - Project No. 0225: Art Education, 1984 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 14)
  - Project No. 0207: Art Gallery, 1983 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 15)
  - Project No. 4250: Continuing education, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 16)
  - Conferences and Institutes, 1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 17)
  - College of Arts, 1986 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 18)
  - Project No. 0241: Dance, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 19)
  - School of Music, 1986 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 20)
  - Department of Theatre, 1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 21)
  - Photography and Cinema, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 22)
  - Biological Sciences, 1986 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 23)
  - Department of Microbiology, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 24)
  - Project No. 038: Botony, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 25)
  - Zoology, 1996 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 26)
  - Humanities, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 27)
  - Slavic Center, 1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 28)
  - Project No. 0600-89120: College of Mathematical Sciences, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 29)
  - Project No. 0628: Department of Chemistry, 1985 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 30)
  - Project No. 0656-89126: Department of Geology, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 31)
  - Project No. 0704-90028: WOSU, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 32)
  - University Press, 1986-1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 33)
  - Project No. 0290: Mershon Auditorium, 1982, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 34)
  - Project No. 0722: Economics, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 35)
  - Project No. 0722: Economics, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 36)
  - Project No. 0788: Communications, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 37)
  - Project No. 0745-90049: Lantern, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 38)
  - Political Science, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 39)
  - Agricultural Technical Inst., 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 40)
  - Lima Campus, 1984, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 41)
  - Project No. 0956: Marion Campus, 1981, 1984-1985 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 42)
  - Project No. 0971: Newark, 1981, 1985-1986 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 43)
  - Project No. 1000: College of Business, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 44)
  - Project No. 1050: Marketing, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 45)
  - Business Research and Support Services, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 46)
  - Project No. 1077: School of Public Policy, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 47)
  - Farm Science Review, 1981 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 48)
  - Agricultural Education, 1986, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 49)
  - Project No. 1163: Horticulture, 1985,1988,1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 50)
  - School of Natural Resources, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 51)
  - ERIC, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 52)
  - School of Health, Physical Education, 1989,1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 53)
  - Engineering Admin., 1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 54)
  - Women in Engineering, 1986 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 55)
  - Department of Aviation, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 56)
  - Computer and Information Science, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 57)
  - Department of Electrical Engineering, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 58)
  - Engineering Experiment Station, 1988, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 59)
  - Department of Industrial and Systems Engin, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 60)
  - Materials Science Engineering, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 61)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1990, 1993 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 62)
  - Textiles and Clothing, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 63)
  - College of Nursing, 1986 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 64)
  - College of Pharmacy, 1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 65)
  - College of Social Work, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 66)
  - Dental Clinic, 1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 67)
  - College of Dentistry, 1987, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 68)
  - Dental Clinic, 1982 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 69)
  - Dental Clinic, 1982 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 70)
  - Medical Basic Sciences, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 71)
  - College of Medicine, 1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 72)
  - School of Allies Medical Professions, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 73)
  - Biomedical Communications Div., 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 74)
  - Department of Radiology, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 75)
  - Veterinary Medicine, 1979, 1981,1982,19886,1987,1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 76)
  - Veterinary Pathobiology, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 77)
  - University Libraries, 1981, 1982, 1986, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 78)
  - President, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 79)
  - Office of Career Development, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 80)
  - University Equipment Operational Review, 1981 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 81)
  - Office of Campus Planning and Space Util., 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 82)
  - Agronomy, National Resources and Plant, 1982 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 83)
  - Equipment Inventory, 1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 84)
  - Office of the Treasurer, 1984, 1986, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 85)
  - Fees and Deposits, 1982, 1984, 1986, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 86)
  - Surplus Materials Disposal, 1984, 1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 87)
  - Petty Cash System, 1986 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 88)
  - Scholarship Voucher System, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 89)
  - Division of Accounts Payable, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 90)
  - Materials Research Lab, 1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 91)
  - Patents and Copyrights Admin., 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 92)
  - Minority Affairs, 1986 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 93)
  - Women's Studies, 1977 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 94)
  - Laboratory Animal Review, 1981 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 95)
  - Office of Admissions, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 96)
  - University Registrar, 1996 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 97)
  - University Center for International Studies, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 98)
  - Center for Teaching Excellence, 1987. 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 99)
  - Purchasing System, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 100)
  - B.A.R.S, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 101)
  - University Systems, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 102)
  - Instructional Research Computer Center, 1986 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 103)
  - Optometry, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 104)
  - Optometry Clinic, 1982 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 105)
  - University Systems, 1986, 1987, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 106)
  - Equipment Services Utilization, 1984 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 107)
  - Wexner Center for the Visual Arts, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 108)
  - Arts and Science Admin., 1978 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 109)
  - Military Science, 1986 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 110)
  - University Registrar, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 111)
  - Registration, Records, and Scheduling, 1984 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 112)
  - Student Organizations, 1983, 1984, 1987, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 113)
  - University Health Services, 1986, 1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 114)
  - University Recreation, 1978, 1985, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 115)
  - Personnel Services Admin., 1987, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 116)
  - Child Care Services, 1981, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 117)
  - Development Fund, 1986 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 118)
  - OSU Campaign, 1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 119)
  - Reproduction Research and Education, 1985 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 120)
  - Air Transportation, 1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 121)
  - University Name and Seal Royalty, 1983 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 123)
  - Contracts Administration, 1986 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 124)
  - Business Management, 1983 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 125)
  - Purchasing Department, 1984, 1986, 1987, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 126)
  - Receiving, 1984 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 127)
  - Grounds Maintenance, 1982, 1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 128)
  - Physical Facilities, 1987, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 129)
  - University Public Safety, 1984, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 130)
  - Traffic and Parking, 1985, 1988, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 131)
  - Stores, 1981, 1982, 1988 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 132)
  - Receiving, 1984 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 133)
  - Architects Office, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 134)
  - University Vehicles, 1987 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 135)
  - Project No. 5165-90057: Reprographics, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 136)
  - Project No. 5182-91090: UNITS, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 137)
  - Project No. 5200: Residence and Dining, 1981, 1982, 1984, 1985, 1987, 1989 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 138)
  - Project No. 5164: Printing Facility, 1985, 1989, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 139)
  - Project No. 5260: North Commons, 1982 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 140)
  - Project No. 5250: Residence and Dining Halls Bus. Ofc., 1982 (Box UA.2000.0077.0017, Folder 141)